Do you think your generation failed on October 7?
We failed because we did a lot of things,
and October 7 happened.
We didn't kill anyone, we didn't rape anyone,
but...
we didn't do enough things to avoid it.
We talked a lot against the wars,
and it was not right.
Maybe, the October 7th,
maybe if we had done much more things,
before...
Maybe, maybe,
we would be sitting here in another situation,
another conversation.
But we failed.
We took the the wrong decisions.
It's my generation,
it's my government.
I don't care about them.
They are just...
actors in this game.
If we would...
if we were...
If we had done it in another way,
Maybe all this would never have come onto the world.
All those damage, all those deaths
on these pictures.
Yuval had his 29ths birthday,
just a day before October 7th
Yuval was the favorite of my grandsons,
they called him in Hebrew:
"Dod Yuvi", uncle Yuvi
He's not from our family, but they called him.
They liked him. Maybe he would still be here,
him and his generation would (still) be here,
if we had taking other decisions.
The hard ones.
We chose
the easy one: "Just to do peace".
Now there will be no peace.